i just recently turned 50. i i don't
like getting older here's what i've
noticed i'm using my shirt pocket all
the time
i've never used that in my life can't
stop
as recently as a couple years ago if i'd
have seen you had stuff in your shirt
pocketbook what a dork
how people like you got a paper clip i
sure do yeah i got
i got standard and jumbo what are you
looking for
we get ugly stuff growing out of us
right ear hair
come on ladies we know you don't like it
okay nobody warns us i took biology in
high school nobody said a word about the
whisk brooms
that would shoot out the side of my head
one day
walking around the house knocking
pictures off the wall
and it's not normal here it's this 500
pound test line
it's the same stuff they land marlins
with down in the keys
my waist oh my gosh can't you just get
rid of it no you can't i've tried to
pull them out
it's the most painful thing i've ever
done in my life they're connected to
your spinal cord
i was in the mall i yanked when i did
most motor skills for about an hour
trying to call for help
here's where you know you're getting
ugly is when people stop recognizing you
have you had that
a couple weeks ago walking across the
living room in my underwear
my oldest daughter goes hey grandma what
i don't know what's worse that i'm
starting to look like my mother-in-law
or that she walks around the kids in
boxers in no time
parents don't make you feel good about
getting older i told you my dad passed
away my mom is still around
but my mom we've noticed over the last
year she's been slipping a little bit no
christmas time she goes what do you want
from santa
oh i told you two weeks ago what i
wanted from santa
you've got to start writing this down
conversations with your parents to the
worst the conversations i'd have with my
dad at the end of his life were the same
ones we had when i was about six
the roles just flip around we would go
out to eat
walk into a restaurant i would look at
my dad and go she wasn't sitting right
here
don't touch anything don't talk to
anybody i'll be back in a minute all
right
where are your shoes
it's 50 degrees i don't have any shoes
on
what do you want to eat a reuben not a
chance now
you make a mess i'm not putting up with
that crap today
[Music]
you're getting chicken strips and a cup
of juice with a lid on it that's it all
right
go wash up thank you very much
[Applause]
local man robs wendy's with alligator
for the alligator boys now
[Music]
mom